We just talked about ear points to quit smoking.
And there's also body point to help quit smoking.
One of the most important body point to quit smoking is on the hand, and it's called a Tim Mee point.
How we can locate this Tim Mee point?
So this is the hand.
The Tim Mee point is between this, on a transverse line, there's a point called a large intestine 5.
So when you move your finger like this, and between these two tendons, that's one point.
And then, 1.5 inch above this transverse line is called lung 7.
Those two points, in the middle it's the Tim Mee point.
This Tim Mee point we can use that to quit smoking.
So, if we use the needles, going upward to the lung direction and then we thread needle underneath the skin and if we can go point three, point five inches, we can stimulate two points.
One is Tim Mee point, the other is Lung 7.
And the good thing about this point is we can leave the needles here for even a couple of hours if the patient is comfortable.
So we can tape there and leave it there to continue stimulate the point because this is on a lung channel, so that help the lung function.